{
    "id": "0f171bd1dfd24c36b86a602f7f97335e",
    "title": "Unless, Providing, Provided That, And As Long As Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "346f547da19547ef86103c07aea31be3",
            "title": "Unless, Providing, Provided, And As Long As Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "We can win the championship, .......................... we avoid bad injuries.",
                    "description": "Providing has a similar meaning to if.",
                    "answers": [
                        "providing",
                        "Unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will leave now, .............................. there is anything left to do now.",
                    "description": "Unless has a similar meaning to if not. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "as long as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We can hold the party in the garden ............................. it doesn't rain.",
                    "description": "Provided means on condition that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "provided",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The public will be admitted to the galleries, ........................... they make a donation.",
                    "description": "Providing means on condition that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "providing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can keep the puppy ................................... you promise to take care of it.",
                    "description": "Both expressions are possible here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "as long as",
                        "provided that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can take my car ............................... you drive carefully.",
                    "description": "As long as and provided that mean 'on condition that'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "as long as",
                        "provided that",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can't help you ............................ you tell me what is wrong.",
                    "description": "Unless means if not. The above sentence can also be written as: I can help you if you tell me what is wrong. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "providing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can help you ............................... you tell me what is wrong.",
                    "description": "Provided that means on condition that.",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "provided that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He wouldn't eat anything .................................. he cooked it himself.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "providing",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can take this seat, ............................... no one has reserved it.",
                    "description": "Providing and as long as are possible here. They both mean 'on condition that'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "unless",
                        "providing",
                        "as long as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "My parents don't care who I marry .......................... I am happy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as long as",
                        "unless"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You can go out now .............................. you finish your homework first.",
                    "description": "All of these expressions mean the same,",
                    "answers": [
                        "providing",
                        "provided that",
                        "as long as",
                        "All of these"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}